[
          {
            "question": "1. Which planet is closest to the Sun?",
            "options": ["Venus", "Mercury", "Earth","Mars"],
            "answer": "Mercury"
          },
          {
            "question": "2. Which data structure organizes items in a First-In, First-Out (FIFO) manner?",
            "options": ["Stack", "Queue", "Tree"," Graph"],
            "answer": "Queue"
          },
          {
            "question": "3. Which of the following is primarily used for structuring web pages?",
            "options": ["Python", "Java", "HTML","C++"],
            "answer": "HTML"
          },
          {
            "question": "4. Which chemical symbol stands for Gold?",
            "options": ["Au", "Gd", "Ag","Pt"],
            "answer": "Au"
          },
          {
            "question": "5. Which of these processes is not typically involved in refining petroleum?",
            "options": ["Fractional distillation", "Cracking", "Polymerization","Filtration"],
            "answer": "Filtration"
          },
          
            {
              "question": "6. What is the value of 12 + 28?",
              "options": ["30", "40", "50", "60"],
              "answer": "40"
            },
            {
              "question": "7. How many states are there in the United States?",
              "options": ["48", "49", "50", "51"],
              "answer": "50"
            },
            {
              "question": "8. In which year was the Declaration of Independence signed?",
              "options": ["1776", "1789", "1801", "1754"],
              "answer": "1776"
            },
            {
              "question": "9. What is the value of pi rounded to the nearest integer?",
              "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "10. If a car travels at 60 mph for 2 hours, how many miles does it travel?",
              "options": ["100", "110", "120", "130"],
              "answer": "120"
            }
          
        ]
        